Nana Johnson

User Interface and User Experience Designer with over five years of experience in art and design. Collaborated with a creative team to design and produce quality products. Ability to create designs with consideration to user needs and technical limitations.

Dallas, TX 75287 (469) 765-5513 nanajohnsondesign@gmail.com nanajohnsondesign.com

EXPERIENCE

Julie Cohn Design, Dallas — Assistant Production Manager

APRIL 2015 - JULY 2020

Designed, fabricated, assembled, and quality assured jewelry products.

- Analyzed and researched new techniques to problem solve design issues.
- Streamlined prototyping and production methods, slashing budget and time by 40%.
- Developed an inventory and workflow system for the team to track production and time requirements.
- Demonstrated time and resource management skills under tight deadlines.
- Trained and supervised new employees.

Sterling Health Center, Dallas — *Receptionist*

JULY 2017 - DECEMBER 2017

Self-driven, organized, and efficient front desk receptionist skilled in verbal and written communication.

- Professionally communicated with clients through phone calls, writing, and in person correspondence.
- Maintained booking, membership, and client intake records.
- Developed and centralized company service records, increasing internal productivity by 30%.

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at Dallas, Richardson — Bachelor of Arts in Arts, Technology, and Emerging Communication

IANUARY 2018 - MAY 2020

Brookhaven College, Farmers Branch — Associate of Arts

IANUARY 2015 - DECEMBER 2017

SKILLS

User Interface

User Experience

Interaction Design

Visual Design

User Research

Usability Testing

Wireframing

Prototyping

3D Modeling and Rendering

Motion Graphics

HTML / CSS / JavaScript

Fine and Studio Arts

TOOLS

Adobe Creative Cloud

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Premiere Pro

Adobe XD

Autodesk Maya

Autodesk Mudbox

Substance Painter

Substance Designer